= kisskh.asia =
"The Last Oath"
(Episode 3: Guangqi Terminal)
Thanks, man.
What are you doing?
Lin Zai.
Why didn't you say you were hurt?
It's just a scratch.
Thanks for the help.
We need to hurry back to camp.
Take this bag of supplies as a reward.
I don't need your supplies.
With that leg injury, Lin
Zai definitely can't walk.
And you're badly injured too.
Man, I'm stuck carrying
both the supplies and Lin Zai.
If we run into danger on the way back...
We probably won't be able to handle it.
Lead the way.
We're lucky this guy saved us today.
If we're sure he's not a threat,
let's ask if he wants to join our camp.
I agree.
Thanks for saving us today.
You saved me last time.
I'm returning the favor.
Now we're even.
See, I told you.
Good deeds pay off.
I almost thought we
were going to die today.
No.
It probably would've been
a fate worse than death.
What's your name?
I'm Lin Zai. 'Lin' as in two woods,
and 'Zai' as in present.
A-Leh.
'Lie' as in raging fire.
That's pretty cool.
Do you usually work alone?
How did you find us?
You talk too much.
I'm just trying to distract
myself by talking to you.
Otherwise, the pain is going to kill me.
Ouch!
Watch your step!
Slow down.
Easy now.
Don't move.
How did this happen?
You were perfectly fine when you left.
Grandma.
I'm fine.
Look, we all made it back in one piece.
Yeah, all thanks to this guy here.
Hey, man.
Need a hand?
Brother Li, can you knock me out?
Even if I knock you out right now,
when I clean your wound later,
the pain will just wake you right back up.
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait!
Let me brace myself first.
Let me brace myself!
You...
I said let me brace myself first!
You didn't even give me a warning!
Hey man, you're pretty pro at this.
I'm used to it.
You guys have had a rough day.
I'll go whip up something good for you.
I'll go.
You stay here and look after them.
This guy is a jack-of-all-trades.
He's totally my idol.
You're not too bad yourself.
Hey.
Your wound-dressing skills
are getting more and more professional.
You bet.
Does that make me an idol too?
You're nuts.
Yeah.
Hey, man.
Your cooking is out of this world.
Thanks again for lending a hand today.
I apologize for what happened before.
We all got what we needed.
We're even.
The generator died again.
I'll go take a look.
Mm.
Sit still.
Do you want to lose that leg?
I'm the only one here
who knows how to fix it.
It's an old issue, won't take long.
I'll fix it.
Where is it?
You...
Hey.
Why don't you two just go together?
Stop dawdling.
Here.
It's right over there.
I won't trouble you.
Aside from being a man of few words
and looking a bit cold,
you really can't find a single flaw in him.
If he's willing to join our camp,
that would be fantastic news.
Lin Zai really found a treasure.
If anything, let's have Lin Zai
find a chance to ask him again.
If he doesn't want to stay,
we'll give him some supplies
and send him off properly.
Makes sense.
Alright, alright.
Let's eat.
You'll feel awful if you catch a cold.
Why are you...
Did you really think you
were being quiet all night?
Sorry about that.
Does your leg still hurt?
It's much better now.
Why don't you go back down and rest?
I'll go catch up on sleep
once the sun comes up.
It's fine.
Your camp is very safe.
Just being here
is restful enough.
Looks like you haven't had it easy either,
if this is enough to satisfy you.
My home
used to be right along this coastline.
About five or six kilometers east.
The house was tiny.
My parents,
me,
and my older brother.
The four of us crammed in there together.
Even though life was tough,
we had a lot of beautiful memories.
Have you ever gone back to look?
I'm the only one left alive now.
When the apocalypse hit,
my parents didn't make it.
Later on,
I watched my brother
die right in front of me.
Even if I went back to that house,
I could never go back to how things were.
Life still has to go on.
I know.
I just miss them so much.
They used to put me first in everything.
Especially my brother.
He was always so protective of me.
If only I had your skills
then I could have protected him.
His death
wasn't your fault.
In the face of disaster,
we all did our best.
Look.
The sun is coming up.
A-Leh.
Do you want to stay?
I still have a lot of
important things to do.
I was just asking.
Alright.
It's dawn.
I'm going back to catch up on some sleep.
Make yourself at home.